

# **Erfan Sheikh**

## Game Developer | Technical Artist

#### **About Me**

A Technical Artist / 3d Generalist with vast GameDev experience in various projects. Experienced Unity3d developer and tech-artist. Creator at heart, Good team player and a self-learner. Very interested in seeing and experiencing new tools and techniques and make beautiful results.

#### **Professional Experience**

اردیبهشت استودیو | Ordibehesht Studio 2018 – 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Delivering 3d assets and game assets for casual games.
- Create Shaders and VFX.
- Prepare interns and junior artists to work on projects.
- Create and maintain different pipelines for delivering high quality assets.
- manage a small (5-7) in-house art team.

Joyixir Studio 2021 - 2023

Key responsibilities:

- Game development and technical art.
- Make more than 40 hypercasual games over 2 years.

Pensor Studio 2016 - 2018

- Motion Graphics Artist
- Design 3d ad videos.

#### **My Contact**

Erfan.sheikhhoseini@gmail.com

**(L)** +98 937 9260049

in/erfan-sheikhhoseini

My Website

#### **Hard Skill**

- Technical Artist | 3d Modeling | Shaders
- Unity Developement | C# | Python
- Texture Painting | Substance Painter
- Character Rigging and animation
- Tools Programming | Pipeline Management

#### **Soft Skill**

- Team Work
- Team Lead
- Flexible
- Problem Solver
- Autonomous

### **Education Background**

Barajin/Qazvin
Bachelor of Computer Science
Completed in 2017

**Achievements** 

4Wheelers

Best Multiplayer Game On IMGA